Translated by Releska
But in the end, I keep my dream of being a boy
Of course, you and I always are together
I'll be there, I'll be there
I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there
I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there
I'll be there, I'll be there
It takes some time, whenever we meet
Yeah, right
You and me, you too
If we were loved by each other
Rumors are open in reality
Which complements the feelings of happiness
Missing you
I'm glad you're here!
I'm here to see you!
Everyone, please come in!
I'm not going to forget!
I'm just going to have a ride with my mom!
I'll be back soon!
I'm so glad!
But I'm sure you're in a good mood!
I wanted to go with you if you didn't have a visa.
What are you doing?
We're gonna have to play a game with the other two of them.
We got a bad idea.
Father, aren't we gonna invite them?
Yes, we'll invite them.
Hazuki, we'll see each other in the next episode.
I know!
Let's go!
What has happened in the last night?
Hello?
Good weather. Welcome.
Really?
The iron fabric is difficult to blow.
Naisu is a bad air-coat.
Do you think you can do it in other places?
Of course you can.
Why don't you just leave for a while?
My father hasn't been on his way to the cabin.
He's wearing a beard and hiking together.
He's cool!
He's so cool!
I'll go for it if I die!
You're not a good guy, right?
Even if you hit it, you'll be punished.
Yes!
Stop!
I'm not going to be mad at you!
That is...
Everyone, are you alright?
Zedaren...
What, the store!
Oh, well.
If they think this is a washroom, the store is important, isn't it?
Yeah, the shopkeepers' people do have a lot of tricks.
What's the matter?
We don't need to worry about that.
I came to the car to drive the taxi.
I've been driving for a long time now, just for the sake of my dad.
That's a shame for you guys.
We're going to be at the beach too.
The beach is really cold.
Yes, we're going to drive the taxi.
And we're going to go to the day-in-bomb.
Then we'll be back for the day-in-bomb.
Let's go.
Then, let's go.
Bye-bye.
Taku, let's go to the mountain!
Where's the mountain mountain?
It's the mountain of the island.
Hey, let's go to the mountain of the island.
Let's go to the mountain of the island.
The mountain of the island is so beautiful.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
That red and yellow one is the mountain of the island.
It's the mountain of the island.
Oh, it's getting closer to the mountain.
Yeah.
It's a strong environment.
It's a big, touching environment.
It's so big.
The sea is beautiful because it's below the mountain.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a big, touching environment.
Hey, the sea is beautiful because it's below the mountain.
What are you doing, Baka?
Yes, let's take a look.
I don't know if I'm going to the mountain.
Yes, one, two!
Let's go to the next one.
Yes, let's go.
Fukumuka, why aren't you doing it properly?
Hey, Ko-Zan.
Wait, I'm going to go to the mountain this time.
That's good.
And I'll take my mother.
What?
Yo-chan?
Wow!
I saw this when I was a child.
Then, please.
Yeah.
I want to go to the mountain.
Let's go.
It's delicious.
I'm going to the mountain.
Wait.
What are you thinking about?
Hey!
Everyone, I want to go to the mountain.
I like it.
I don't think it's good.
It's okay.
It's because there's an expression.
Look.
Huh?
Is it really heavy?
Is it really coming out?
I want to see it.
Let's go.
Here it is.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What?
Did you come out?
Why?
Why are you taking care of me?
Fukumuka!
Stop it!
What?
Let me go.
I'm a real kid.
It's something.
You said the same thing to me.
Because I was interested,
I couldn't figure out what I was doing.
Let me go.
Huh?
This woke up can be the same.
What?
I'm really glad we got along together.
It's a summer day, so it's really late.
Hurry, go home.
Go, go home.
You're definitely going to go home too.
We'll also go home.
We'll go home soon.
I'll see you next time.
Bye bye Kojika-chan.
Bye bye.
Kanal
Don't come near me!
Oh, no! It's Aitsuma Aigo!
I've been waiting for you for a while.
Huh? Is it Aigo's?
It looks like that.
I'm sure you'll be able to follow us.
But what do you think?
I'm sure you'll find me, but...
Hey, don't do this to me!
If you say that, you'll get angry too.
I'm so cute.
But how do you find your dad?
I don't know how to do it.
It's like a TV show.
I don't know.
I don't know how to do it.
I heard that I was going to live in a TV show
so I'm going to give it to you.
Roating
Would you like to eat up?
It's okay.an人 is busy
Dig a little machine
Roating
Roating! Where are you going, Roating?
You're so boring.
Why are you ethereal?
Yeah.
I'm coming back when I'm blind.
Hey, Yo
If you do something like this, don't you think it was a dream?
Huh?
Really?
Yeah!
Well then...
It's true.
It's on this side, isn't it?
What?
That one?
Huh?
It's on this side?
It's on this side.
Hey you!
It's on this side!
Yeah!
Director, please...
I want to eat something.
Please enjoy eating.
I'll be back again!
Woman!
I can't!
Please wait!
Oh, I see!
You look so happy, Mika!
Who's in the way of the ant?
Why are you here?
I'm here to teach you!
I'm going to the castle!
Oh, you said that!
What's going on?
I can't believe it!
I'm here!
Muka Muka, here you are!
Hey, aren't you going to have barbecue?
I have some food for you.
I'm going to have some food for you.
Yeah, everyone!
So, you're going to have a cute little girl.
You're going to have a cute little girl.
I'm going to have a big party for you.
Oh, right!
You two are so delicious!
I'm going to have a barbecue!
I'm going to have a barbecue for you!
Maybe that girl is a big girl!
That's right!
It's a fun sports car!
So, Muka, I'm going to have a barbecue for you.
A car?
Alright, I'm going to have a barbecue!
Let's go!
That's not easy!
If you've got one that suits you and don't destroy this outfit,
you're going to get lucky with whatets you go on every day.
You have to have a barbecue if you do cross the existing state.
Yeah, but...
You can't have a barbecue for the food.
So, what a request!
What exactly are you doing!
You've got to meet yourself, huh?!
Miss Lankasugu told you to go get her food!
I'll take it back.
Is that fish?
I'm not going to eat it yet.
I want that fish.
Arang-san, please wait for me.
Bo-chan, get up.
Oh, no.
I really have something to eat.
Muka-muka, we're going to have a chat tonight.
Muka-muka, do you know the answer?
It's like I'm talking to you.
Wow, what are you doing?
Let's talk to each other.
Where are you going?
I'm not going to sleep either.
Muka-muka!
I did it!
The telepathy is getting worse.
Really?
I don't know where to go.
It's okay to go anywhere, but you can't come to me.
Are you scared?
It's not like that.
It's getting worse, isn't it?
Is it here?
Is there a father here?
Muka-muka!
Huh?
What's wrong, Muka-chan?
Maybe Muka-muka had something to eat.
It's a big deal, isn't it?
It looks like it's going to be delicious.
Muka-muka!
I'm going to eat it.
Where is Muka-muka?
Muka-muka!
Where is it?
Huh?
It's the temperature of the chicken.
Look at that.
Let's eat it with the temperature.
Wait!
I'll give you a chance.
What do you want?
About SNS,
Crows.
What do you want?
Why are you giving me this shrimp?
Snack?
Listen!
I don't know how to eat it.
Swallow.
Just However it seems I'm a fishing star or a fishing star.
Really?
Baaakka!
You're not a man anymore!
Huh?
Hey, you're a good guy, aren't you?
Hey, what kind of doggy are you going to talk to?
What are you talking about?
Let's talk about it together.
Now!
Oh no!
I did it!
This is the 8th floor!
Please enter the 4th floor!
Please!
You did it too!
Now I'm getting better and better!
I've been using it for a long time!
Lanka!
Why are you so famous for that?
That's right!
What is it?
What's wrong, Lanka?
I don't know!
Why are you so famous for that?
Sir, I'm leaving!
Hey, I'm coming!
Everyone!
This is the first time I die!
I'm going to die!
Goodbye!
Where am I?
Really, this place?
Wow!
It's there!
Huh?
It's so late!
I also worried about my mother and I was looking for her!
What do you want?
What were you going to do?
I don't want to be here anymore!
Runaway's a good-called
Runaway is a good-bye to the Black River.
Huh?
What the..?
During the war...
Gah!
Runaway is a good-bye to the Black River!
Where's the other barrier?
He's dead.
He's dead...
Runaway's a good-bye to the Black River.
Wh-What happened?
H-What happened?
What's going on?
I'm going to hit you!
Wow...
I'm getting wet!
I'm going to hit you!
Ah!
Look! The mother is here!
Now, let's go. We'll be in front of you now.
Hello! We're back!
What? You're lying, aren't you? I don't know what's going on.
I was walking around with the other one, so I got to see the plane.
What do we do?
I'm not that good at it.
You're not that good at it.
What?
I'm not that good at it.
You can't really imagine what you're going to do.
Oh, what are you doing?
I'm not really good at it.
I'm not that good at it.
M-M-M-M-M-M-M!
I wonder if you know how to change it.
You're making a lot of money, aren't you?
Yeah.
It's about the first time you're in the present.
It's a bit of a telepathy.
It's a genius to be with everyone.
Oh! You're back!
How did you say that?
It's not that bad.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Huh?
It's not that bad.
Everyone's been eating all the food.
I'm hungry.
No way!
It's not that bad!
It's not that bad.
But you've been eating all the food in the car, right?
It's been a long time since I've eaten.
Huh?
Do you want to eat more?
Yeah.
Is it fun to eat?
Yeah!
Let's eat together again.
Huh?
Is it like this?
Yeah.
It's not that bad.
Excuse me.
Is it bread?
Shall we eat it?
Oh, I'm saved.
I was waiting for you.
Oh, it's pretty good.
We're going to the helicopter now.
The helicopter?
Huh?
You're going to the helicopter next time, right?
Yeah, that's right.
B!
Let's eat!
Huh?
You're going to the helicopter next time, right?
Yeah, it's a helicopter.
Let's eat first.
I wonder if that's possible.
What?
If you're going to eat it, you can eat it.
Yeah, I got it.
Excuse me, Mr. Rokka.
I can't believe it.
Okay then.
I know.
We're going to the helicopter next time.
The helicopter?
I'm going to the helicopter next time.
There's a helicopter.
It's heart
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang
I'll make it easy, easy, easy, easy, easy
I'll make it easy, everything looks so nice
I'll make it fun
I'll make a story
Translated by bee
Hey you guys, Itadakimasu!
Uma-chan! This is bigger than Umas, I can't see!
No, no, no, no!
This is a surprise, so you can't ride it!
Uwaaaah!
Oh no!
I'm tired.
Next time, I'll be on my way to the Muka Muka Muka!
I'll be on my way to the Muka Muka Muka!